# Shubham Bansal

## Get in touch!

### Mobile:

+91-7737278724

#### Email:

Shubhambansalo96@gmail.com

### Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/s hubham-bansal-86b1a1209/

#### Github:

https://github.com/Shubham-Bansal47

## **Education**

## **LNMIIT** Jaipur:

B.TECH | Electronics and Communication Engineering 2020 - 2024

-> CG - 6.98

# Specializations (Skills)

- -> C/C++ (Certified)
- -> Data Structures and Algorithms in C++(Certified)

-> HTML/CSS

# Non-Technical Skills

- -> Communication
- -> Public Speaking
- -> Analytical Decision Making
- -> Creative Problem Solving
- -> Teamwork

# Extracuricular Activities

## **About Me**

A technophile interested in exploring new domains related to marketing and technology, currently working on my coding and data structures and algorithmic skills as it galvanizes me, worked as a Social Media Marketing Intern and Campus Ambassador for 2 different startups. Interacting with people and learning new things from them excites me. Its the curiosity in me that makes me want to gain more knowledge that will pump me up.

## **Work Experience**

## Social Media Marketing Intern:

| Arbitrium | 1st June 2020 - 31st July 2020

-> Worked closely with the marketing head for digital marketing promotions, me and my team revamped their promotion techniques and it hyped by 15% growth.

## **Campus Ambassador:**

| PECFEST | 2020 - 2021

- -> Collected valuable feedback from college student about their interests in different fields and promoted PECFEST in LNMIIT Jaipur.
- -> Helped Punjab Engineering College Chandigarh to spread their programs and fests information to get registrations from students for easiness in it's conduction.

## **Achievements/Awards**

# **LNMIIT Jaipur:**

-> Got 1st position in the very 1st event of Entrepreneurship cell (Yellow Pages Event), Basically the team with the best pitching wins the show.

# **Coding Platforms:**

- -> Solved 191 problems in almost 55 days on Codeforces.
  - Codeforces ID: https://codeforces.com/profile/Codemon-47
- -> 1600 rating on Codechef.
- Codechef ID: https://www.codechef.com/users/badboy\_47
- -> 3 star on HackerRank.
  - HackerRank ID: https://www.hackerrank.com/shubhambansal096
  - Badminton (Silver medal on district level)
  - Relay race (Bronze medal in school)
    - Singing